     2017-03-07	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

            CPD	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	      B-A0	(S1(NP(NP*
  investigating	       VBG	      S-VP	         O	  investigating	       S-V	      I-A0	*
       shooting	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      E-A0	*)
           that	       WDT	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	    S-R-A0	(SBAR(WHNP*)
        injured	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	        injured	      I-A1	       S-V	(S(VP*
              4	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
         people	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
       WTVM.com	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
       Columbus	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
             GA	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*
           News	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
        Weather	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
              &	        CC	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
         Sports	      NNPS	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	*)))))))

       COLUMBUS	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      B-A0	         O	(S1(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	*
             GA	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	(NP(NP*)
              (	     -LRB-	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	(PRN*
           WTVM	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	(NP*)
              )	     -RRB-	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	*)
            –	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	         O	*)
       Columbus	       NNP	      I-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A0	         O	(SBAR(S(NP*
         police	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	         O	*)
            are	       VBP	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
      searching	       VBG	      E-VP	         O	      searching	       S-V	         O	(VP*
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(NP(NP*
         person	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*)
    responsible	        JJ	    S-ADJP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(ADJP*
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A1	*)
           that	       WDT	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	    S-R-A1	(SBAR(WHNP*)
           took	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           took	      I-A1	       S-V	(S(VP*
          place	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      S-A2	(NP*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
           32nd	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
         Avenue	       NNP	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  E-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      E-A1	      S-A1	*))))))))))))))))

      According	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-ADV	         O	(S1(S(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	         O	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	         O	(NP*
         police	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	         O	*
         report	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-ADV	         O	*)))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
         police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	         O	(NP*)
           were	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
         called	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	         called	       S-V	         O	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	         O	(PP*
        Midtown	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A2	         O	(NP*
        Medical	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A2	         O	*
         Center	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      E-A2	         O	*))
      regarding	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A0	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A0	*)
           that	       WDT	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	    S-R-A0	(SBAR(WHNP*)
        injured	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	        injured	      I-A1	       S-V	(S(VP*
           four	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(NP*
         people	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A1	*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
         Sunday	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*))))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-TMP	*
          March	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
              5	        CD	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  E-AM-TMP	*)
         around	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
              3	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           a.m.	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	*
        NEWLINE	        NN	      E-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      E-A1	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))

           This	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
           case	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
        remains	       VBZ	      S-VP	         O	        remains	       S-V	(VP*
          under	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A3	(PP*
  investigation	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      E-A3	(NP*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	         O	*)))))

      Copyright	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*
           2017	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
          WTVM.	        NN	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	*))

            All	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         rights	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       reserved	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	       reserved	       S-V	(VP*)
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

