     2017-01-19	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

            Boy	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(S(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	*
             15	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	*)
           shot	        NN	      S-VP	         O	              -	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	(PP*
      Englewood	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	(NP*)))))

            Boy	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
             15	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
           shot	        NN	      S-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
      Englewood	       NNP	      S-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      B-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      I-A1	*)
              A	        DT	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
        15-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(ADJP*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
            boy	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*))))
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	(VP*
       Thursday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(NP*
          night	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
          South	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Side	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
      Englewood	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
   neighborhood	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A1	*))))))

             At	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(S1(S(PP*
           8:53	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           p.m.	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP*
            boy	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	(VP*
       multiple	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(NP*
          times	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
          chest	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
            and	        CC	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        abdomen	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
           6900	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
        Stewart	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
      according	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-ADV	(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(PP*
        Chicago	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(NP*
         Police	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  E-AM-ADV	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             He	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
          taken	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	          taken	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-MNR	(PP*
          Comer	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(NP*
       Children	       NNP	      E-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*
           ’s	        JJ	      B-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*
       Hospital	        NN	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(PP*
       critical	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(NP*
      condition	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-MNR	*))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A1	(NP*)))

     Additional	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(S(NP*
        details	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	*)
           were	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	              -	(VP*
            not	        RB	         O	         O	              -	*
    immediately	        RB	    B-ADJP	         O	              -	(ADJP*
      available	        JJ	    E-ADJP	         O	              -	*))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	*))

