     2017-01-11	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

         Victim	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(NP(NP(NP*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
     Accidental	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       Shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))
          Flown	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	          Flown	       S-V	(S(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A4	(PP*
          Fargo	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      E-A4	(NP*))))))

         Victim	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(NP(NP(NP*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
     Accidental	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       Shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))
          Flown	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	          Flown	       S-V	(S(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A4	(PP*
          Fargo	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A4	(NP*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A4	*))))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(S1(S(NP*
         Wilkin	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
         County	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
        Sheriff	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      E-A0	*)
        reports	       VBZ	      S-VP	         O	        reports	       S-V	(VP*
             an	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
          rural	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
        Foxhome	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)))
      Wednesday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        January	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
             11	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))

             by	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(S1(PP(PP*
            Joe	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-PER	              -	      I-A0	(NP(NP*
         Radske	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-PER	              -	      I-A0	*)
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-PER	              -	      I-A0	*
   BRECKENRIDGE	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	      I-A0	(NP*)))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	*
             MN	       NNP	      S-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A0	(NP(NP*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A0	*)
            The	       NNP	      B-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A0	(SBAR(S(NP*
         Wilkin	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A0	*
         County	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A0	*
        Sheriff	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A0	*)
        reports	       VBZ	      S-VP	         O	        reports	       S-V	(VP*
             an	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
          rural	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
        Foxhome	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*))
      Wednesday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        January	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
             11	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))))

      According	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	(S1(S(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	(NP*
         report	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	*)))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	       S-V	(VP*
         around	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
           9:19	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           a.m.	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
        NEWLINE	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))

             An	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A0	      B-A0	(S1(S(NP*
     individual	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A0	      E-A0	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	         O	(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	         O	         O	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	         O	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	         O	         O	(NP*
        stomach	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	         O	         O	*))
          while	        IN	    S-SBAR	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	         O	         O	(SBAR*
         trying	       VBG	      B-VP	         O	         trying	  I-AM-TMP	       S-V	         O	(S(VP*
             to	        TO	      I-VP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      B-A1	         O	(S(VP*
          place	        VB	      E-VP	         O	          place	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	       S-V	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
            gun	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	      E-A1	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	      B-A2	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	      I-A2	(NP*
        holster	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      E-A1	      E-A2	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	         O	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	  E-AM-TMP	         O	         O	*)))))))))))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         victim	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
          flown	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	          flown	       S-V	(VP*
             by	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(PP*
            air	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(NP*
      ambulance	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	*))
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(PP*
        Sanford	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A0	(NP*
        Medical	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
         Center	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(PP*
          Fargo	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      E-A0	(NP*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A1	*))))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
       identity	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            and	        CC	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
      condition	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
           were	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
            not	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-NEG	*
       released	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       released	       S-V	(VP*))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

