     2017-01-02	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

            Man	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(X(NP*)
   accidentally	        RB	      B-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-MNR	(VP(ADVP*)
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-MNR	(PP*
           hand	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-MNR	(NP*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
           East	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
       Garfield	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Park	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))

            Man	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP(NP*)
   accidentally	        RB	      B-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-MNR	      I-A1	(VP(ADVP*)
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	      I-A1	*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-MNR	      I-A1	(PP*
           hand	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-MNR	      E-A1	(NP*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
           East	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
       Garfield	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Park	       NNP	      E-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-LOC	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      B-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  E-AM-LOC	*))))
              A	        DT	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      B-A1	(NP*
            man	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	         O	(VP*
   accidentally	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  S-AM-MNR	(ADVP*)
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	  I-AM-TMP	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           hand	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  E-AM-LOC	*
         Monday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  B-AM-TMP	*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	  E-AM-TMP	*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           East	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
       Garfield	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Park	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
   neighborhood	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*))
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           West	       NNP	      I-NP	    B-MISC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Side	       NNP	      E-NP	    E-MISC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	  E-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A1	      S-A1	*))))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(S1(S(NP*
        20-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*
            man	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	         O	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
   accidentally	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-MNR	         O	(VP(ADVP*)
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	         O	*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	         O	(NP*
          right	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	         O	*
           hand	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	         O	*))
             by	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A0	         O	(PP*
        someone	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	      S-A1	(NP(NP*)
             he	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	      S-A0	(SBAR(S(NP*)
           knew	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           knew	      I-A0	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A0	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
            300	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	  I-AM-LOC	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	  I-AM-LOC	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A0	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A0	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
          Homan	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A0	  E-AM-LOC	*))
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
           9:32	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           a.m.	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
      according	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
        Chicago	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	         O	         O	(NP*
         Police	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	         O	         O	*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	         O	         O	*)))))))

             He	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	      B-A1	(S1(S(S(S(NP*)
           took	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           took	       S-V	         O	      I-A1	(VP*
        himself	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	         O	      I-A1	(NP*)
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-DIR	         O	      I-A1	(PP*
          Mount	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-DIR	  B-AM-LOC	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
          Sinai	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-DIR	  I-AM-LOC	      I-A1	*
       Hospital	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-DIR	  E-AM-LOC	      I-A1	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	         O	      I-A1	*
          where	       WRB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	S-R-AM-LOC	      I-A1	(SBAR(WHADVP*)
            his	      PRP$	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	      B-A1	      I-A1	(S(NP*
      condition	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	      E-A1	      I-A1	*)
     stabilized	       VBN	    S-ADJP	         O	     stabilized	  I-AM-DIR	       S-V	      E-A1	(VP*)))))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	         O	         O	*
         police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	         O	      S-A0	(NP*)
           said	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           said	  I-AM-DIR	         O	       S-V	(VP*))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-DIR	         O	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	  E-AM-DIR	         O	       S-V	(NP*)))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A0	      B-A1	(S1(S(S(NP(NP*
         person	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	      I-A1	*)
            who	        WP	      S-NP	         O	              -	    S-R-A0	      I-A1	(SBAR(WHNP*)
           shot	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	      I-A1	(S(VP*
            him	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	      I-A1	(NP*)))))
            was	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(VP*
            not	        RB	         O	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(PP*
        custody	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(NP*))
             as	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(PP*
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(PP*
         Monday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(NP*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	      E-A1	*)))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
         police	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	      S-A0	(NP*)
           said	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           said	         O	       S-V	(VP*)
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

