     2017-03-23	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

         Police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	(S1(S(NP*)
        respond	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	        respond	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(PP*
       shooting	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
        15-year	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP(ADJP*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
            boy	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*))))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            New	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           Port	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
         Richey	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))

            NEW	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      B-A0	(S1(S(NP*
           PORT	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
         RICHEY	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	(VP*
           Fla.	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A0	(X(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	*
          Pasco	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A0	(S(NP(NP*
         County	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
        Sheriff	       NNP	      E-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
             's	       POS	      B-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*)
         Office	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
       deputies	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	*)
            are	       VBP	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
  investigating	       VBG	      E-VP	         O	  investigating	       S-V	(VP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
        15-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(ADJP*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
            boy	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
            New	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
           Port	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	*
         Richey	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A1	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      E-A1	*))))))))))))

         Police	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	(S1(S(NP*)
       received	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       received	       S-V	*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP*
           call	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
          about	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
           near	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
           6400	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
       Limerick	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
         Avenue	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A1	*))
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
           5:11	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           p.m.	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
      according	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-ADV	(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(PP*
      officials	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-ADV	(NP*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A0	(NP*)))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
           teen	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
          flown	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	          flown	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A4	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A4	(NP*
          local	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A4	*
       hospital	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A4	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-LOC	              -	         O	*))))))

             No	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
     additional	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
    information	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            has	       VBZ	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           been	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
       released	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       released	       S-V	(VP*
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
           this	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           time	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	         O	(NP*)))

           This	        DT	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
             is	       VBZ	      S-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	(NP*
     developing	       VBG	      I-NP	         O	     developing	       S-V	*
          story	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	*))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

        Refresh	        VB	      S-VP	         O	        Refresh	       S-V	(S1(S(VP*
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-PNC	(PP*
        updates	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-PNC	(NP*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

