     2017-03-01	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

          Metro	       NNP	      B-NP	     S-ORG	              -	      B-A0	(S1(S(NP*
         police	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	*)
    investigate	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	    investigate	       S-V	(VP*
              2	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
      shootings	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
      overnight	        RB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  S-AM-TMP	(ADVP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
            WMC	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
         Action	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	*
           News	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A1	*
              5	        CD	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
        Memphis	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
      Tennessee	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      E-A1	(NP*)))))))

       Savannah	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        Chatham	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      B-A0	(NP*
          Metro	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*
         Police	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      E-A0	*)
      responded	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	      responded	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(PP*
            two	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       separate	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
      shootings	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*))
      overnight	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	(NP*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A0	*))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
          first	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            one	        CD	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
            900	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
         Mohawk	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
         Street	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

         Police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
            say	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	            say	       S-V	         O	         O	(VP*
            one	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A1	         O	(SBAR(S(NP*
            man	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A1	         O	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	         O	(VP(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	           shot	      I-A1	       S-V	         O	(VP*))
            and	        CC	      I-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	         O	*
            has	       VBZ	      E-VP	         O	            has	      I-A1	         O	       S-V	(VP*
            non	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	      B-A1	(UCP(ADJP*)
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	      I-A1	*
           life	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	      I-A1	(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	      I-A1	*
    threatening	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	      I-A1	(NP*
       injuries	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	      E-A1	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	         O	*))

           They	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
            say	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	            say	       S-V	         O	(VP(VP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A0	(NP*
         victim	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      I-A0	*))
            and	        CC	         O	         O	              -	         O	      I-A0	*
        suspect	        VB	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	      E-A0	(VP*
           knew	       VBD	      E-VP	         O	           knew	         O	       S-V	(S(VP*
           each	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	      B-A1	(NP*
          other	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      E-A1	*
              .	         .	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	         O	         O	*)))))))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         second	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
            300	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
           East	       NNP	      B-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           52nd	       NNP	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
         Street	       NNP	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))

          SCMPD	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      S-A0	(S1(X(S(NP*)
           sent	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           sent	       B-V	(VP*
            out	        RP	     S-PRT	         O	              -	       E-V	(ADVP*)
             an	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
          alert	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
        Twitter	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      I-A1	(NP*))
          about	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))
         around	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(NP(QP*
           3:15	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
           a.m.	        RB	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)
      Wednesday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	      S-A0	(NP*)))

              #	       SYM	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(S1(X(SBAR(WHADVP*)
     SCMPDalert	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-PER	              -	      I-A0	(S(NP*
          SCMPD	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	      E-A0	*)
             is	       VBZ	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
  investigating	       VBG	      E-VP	         O	  investigating	       S-V	(VP*
             an	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
     accidental	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
         300blk	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
              E	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
           52nd	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

            Non	       SYM	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(S(X*)
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
           life	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	(NP*)
    threatening	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	(VP*
       injuries	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	(NP*))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	*))

            —	       SYM	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(S1(S(SBAR*
          SCMPD	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	      I-A0	(S(NP(NP*)
              (	     -LRB-	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	(PRN*
         @scmpd	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(NP*)
              )	     -RRB-	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	*)
          March	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(NP*
              1	        CD	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A0	*
           2017	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(NP(NP*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	      I-A0	*)
            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	(NP*
       victim(s	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A0	*))
              )	     -RRB-	         O	         O	              -	      E-A0	*)
       suffered	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       suffered	       S-V	(VP*
            non	        RB	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(ADVP*)
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
           life	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
    threatening	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*
       injuries	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
        NEWLINE	       NNP	         O	     S-ORG	              -	         O	(NP*)))

      Copyright	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*
           2017	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
          WTOC.	        NN	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	*))

            All	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         rights	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       reserved	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	       reserved	       S-V	(VP*)
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

