     2017-03-16	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

           CMHU	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	      B-A0	(S1(NP(NP*)
  investigating	       VBG	      S-VP	         O	  investigating	       S-V	      I-A0	(VP*
          fatal	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      I-A0	(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	(PP*
         Bendix	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	(NP*)))
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
          ABC57	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	(NP*
           News	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      E-A1	      E-A0	*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
            See	        VB	      S-VP	         O	            See	         O	       S-V	(S(VP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	      B-A1	(NP*
     Difference	       NNP	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
       Michiana	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-PER	              -	         O	      E-A1	*)))))

            One	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(S1(S(S(NP*
            man	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	         O	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
         killed	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	         killed	       S-V	         O	(VP*)))
            and	        CC	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
        another	        DT	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(S(NP*)
        injured	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	      E-A1	*)
           that	       WDT	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	    S-R-A1	(SBAR(WHNP*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	         O	       S-V	(S(VP*
           just	        RB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	  B-AM-TMP	(PP(ADVP*)
          after	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	*
           2:30	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           a.m.	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	*))
       Thursday	       NNP	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           Bend	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-TMP	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      B-A0	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
           Bend	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      I-A0	      I-A1	*
         Police	       NNP	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	      E-A1	*)
      responded	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	      responded	       S-V	         O	(VP(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	         O	(NP(NP*
            800	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	         O	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	         O	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A2	         O	(PP*
         Bendix	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      E-A2	         O	(NP*)))))
            and	        CC	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
        located	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	        located	         O	       S-V	(VP*
        21-year	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	      B-A1	(ADJP*))
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
        Sheldon	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-PER	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
         Andrew	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-PER	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
      Camarillo	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-PER	              -	         O	      I-A1	*)
            and	        CC	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
        25-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(ADJP*)
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	         O	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
          Casey	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-PER	              -	         O	      I-A1	*
         McLean	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	         O	      E-A1	*)
           with	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	  B-AM-MNR	(PP*
        gunshot	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	  I-AM-MNR	(NP*
         wounds	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	  E-AM-MNR	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

           Both	        DT	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
           were	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
          taken	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	          taken	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	(NP*
       hospital	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A2	*))
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-PNC	(PP*
      treatment	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-PNC	(NP*))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

      Camarillo	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
     pronounced	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	     pronounced	       S-V	(VP*
           dead	        JJ	    S-ADJP	         O	              -	      S-A2	(ADJP*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
       hospital	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

         McLean	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	(S1(S(NP*)
             is	       VBZ	      S-VP	         O	              -	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	(PP*
       critical	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	(NP*
      condition	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	*))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A0	(S1(S(NP(NP*
            St.	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
         Joseph	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
         County	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
          Metro	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
       Homicide	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
           Unit	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
           CMHU	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A0	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
      activated	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	      activated	       S-V	         O	(VP*
             to	        TO	      B-VP	         O	              -	  B-AM-PNC	         O	(S(VP*
    investigate	        VB	      E-VP	         O	    investigate	  E-AM-PNC	       S-V	(VP*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

  Investigators	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
            say	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	            say	       S-V	         O	(VP*
           they	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      S-A0	(SBAR(S(NP*)
            are	       VBP	      B-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(VP*
            not	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  S-AM-NEG	*
      searching	       VBG	      E-VP	         O	      searching	      I-A1	       S-V	(VP*
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(PP*
            any	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*
       suspects	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

           They	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(S(NP*)
        believe	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	        believe	       S-V	         O	(VP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A0	(SBAR(S(NP*
            men	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A0	*)
           were	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(VP*
              "	        IN	    S-SBAR	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(VP*
  participating	       VBG	      S-VP	         O	  participating	      I-A1	       S-V	(S(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(PP*
       reckless	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
       behavior	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*)
           with	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*
        firearm	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	*))))))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
              "	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

             An	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
        autopsy	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
           will	        MD	      B-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-MOD	(VP*
             be	        VB	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
      conducted	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	      conducted	       S-V	(VP*
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
      Camarillo	       NNP	      B-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP(NP*
         Friday	       NNP	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
        morning	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
      Kalamazoo	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	(NP*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             If	        IN	    S-SBAR	         O	              -	         O	  B-AM-ADV	(S1(S(SBAR*
            you	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	  I-AM-ADV	(S(NP*)
           have	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	           have	       S-V	  I-AM-ADV	(VP*
            any	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	  I-AM-ADV	(NP(NP*
    information	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	  I-AM-ADV	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	  I-AM-ADV	(PP*
           this	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-ADV	(NP*
           case	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	  E-AM-ADV	*))))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
         please	        VB	      B-VP	         O	         please	         O	       S-V	(VP*
        contact	        NN	      E-VP	         O	              -	         O	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
           CMHU	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	         O	      E-A1	*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
              (	     -LRB-	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PRN*
            574	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(NP*)
              )	     -RRB-	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*)
            235	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
           5009	        CD	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	(NP(NP*)
             or	        CC	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
          Crime	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(NP*
       Stoppers	      NNPS	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))))
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
              (	     -LRB-	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
            574	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(NP*)))
              )	     -RRB-	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

      288-STOP.	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	(S1(NP*))

