     2017-02-09	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

           Teen	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP(NP*
           shot	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	(PP*
          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	(NP*
   Philadelphia	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	*
            rec	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
         center	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	*))))

              A	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
       teenager	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
             is	       VBZ	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
   hospitalized	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	   hospitalized	       S-V	(VP*
          after	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
          South	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
   Philadelphia	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
     recreation	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
         center	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             It	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	       S-V	(VP*
           just	        RB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP(ADVP*)
          after	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
              6	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           p.m.	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*))
      Wednesday	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
           Vare	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP(NP*
     Recreation	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
         Center	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*)
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP(NP*
           1700	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
          South	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           26th	        JJ	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
         Street	        NN	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

         Police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
            say	       VBP	      S-VP	         O	            say	       S-V	         O	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A1	(SBAR(S(NP*
        17-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
           male	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	      I-A1	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
          chest	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

             He	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
          taken	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	          taken	       S-V	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	(PP*
       Children	       NNP	      S-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A2	(NP(NP(NP*
             's	       POS	      B-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A2	*)
       Hospital	       NNP	      E-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A2	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A2	(PP*
   Philadelphia	       NNP	      S-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      I-A2	(NP*))))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A2	(PP*
         stable	        JJ	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	(NP*
      condition	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A2	*))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             No	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
        arrests	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
           have	       VBP	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           been	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           made	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           made	       S-V	(VP*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

