     2017-01-18	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

            2nd	        RB	      B-NP	         O	              -	         O	(S1(S(VP(ADVP*)
        suspect	        VB	      E-NP	         O	              -	         O	*
       arrested	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	       arrested	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP(PP*
        Wagoner	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
             Co	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
           teen	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
             's	       POS	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
          death	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*))
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
           KSWO	        NN	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
         Lawton	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
            OK-	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
        Wichita	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
          Falls	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
             TX	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*))
              :	         :	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
           News	        NN	      S-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	     I-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
        Weather	       NNP	      S-NP	     I-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	     I-ORG	              -	  I-AM-LOC	*
         Sports	       NNP	      S-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  E-AM-LOC	(NP*))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

            ABC	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	(S1(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	*
           24/7	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	*
      Telemundo	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-ORG	              -	(NP*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	*))

        WAGONER	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP(NP*
         COUNTY	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	      I-A1	*
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
             OK	        JJ	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
              (	     -LRB-	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
         KSWO)-	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-PER	              -	      I-A1	*
           Cody	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-PER	              -	      I-A1	*
         Austin	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-PER	              -	      I-A1	*
       Thompson	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	      I-A1	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
             23	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            has	       VBZ	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
           been	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
       arrested	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       arrested	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-MNR	(PP*
     connection	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(NP(NP*)
           with	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(NP(NP*
         murder	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(PP*
        Brennon	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-PER	              -	  I-AM-MNR	(NP(NP*
          Davis	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	*
             15	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-MNR	(NP*))))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

       Thompson	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-PER	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
       arrested	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       arrested	       S-V	(VP*
        January	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(NP*
           17th	        JJ	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	(PP*
             an	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	(NP*
          arson	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	*
      complaint	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A2	*))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

           Josh	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-PER	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP(NP*
     Harrington	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	      I-A1	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
             22	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
       arrested	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       arrested	       S-V	(VP*
     previously	        RB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  S-AM-TMP	(ADVP*)
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-CAU	(PP*
    obstruction	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(NP(NP*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(PP*
        justice	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(NP*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(PP*
     connection	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(NP(NP*)
           with	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-CAU	(NP*
          death	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-CAU	*))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

      According	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-ADV	         O	(S1(S(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	         O	(PP*
         police	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-ADV	         O	(NP*)))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
       Davis’	       NNP	      B-NP	     S-PER	              -	      B-A1	      B-A1	(NP*
           body	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
          found	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	          found	       S-V	         O	(VP*
         burned	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	         burned	    S-C-A1	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
         remote	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
           area	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*)
           near	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
           Fort	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
         Gibson	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-LOC	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Lake	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-LOC	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

      Copyright	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*
           2017	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
          KSWO.	        NN	      E-NP	     S-ORG	              -	*))

            All	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         rights	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       reserved	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	       reserved	       S-V	(VP*)
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

