     2017-04-03	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

         Police	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP(NP(NP*
    Investigate	       NNP	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
           West	       NNP	      I-NP	     B-LOC	              -	*
           Erie	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-LOC	              -	*
       Shooting	       NNP	      E-NP	         O	              -	*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	*
           Erie	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	(NP*
           News	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	*))
            Now	       NNP	      S-NP	         O	              -	*
              :	         :	         O	         O	              -	*
           News	        NN	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	*
        Weather	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	(NP*
              &	        CC	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	*
         Sports	      NNPS	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	*
              |	       POS	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
           WICU	       NNP	      I-NP	     S-ORG	              -	*
             12	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
              &	        CC	      I-NP	         O	              -	*
           WSEE	       NNP	      E-NP	     S-LOC	              -	*))))

         Police	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	(S1(S(NP*)
            are	       VBP	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
  investigating	       VBG	      E-VP	         O	  investigating	       S-V	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	(PP*
           Erie	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
             's	       POS	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*)
           west	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
           side	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             It	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(S1(S(NP*)
       happened	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	       happened	       S-V	(VP*
           just	        RB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	(PP(ADVP*)
          after	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
           9:30	        CD	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
           a.m.	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*))
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP(NP*
            300	        CD	      I-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
          block	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(PP*
           West	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	(NP*
            3rd	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	*
         Street	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	  E-AM-TMP	*)))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             An	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
        18-year	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
              -	         :	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            old	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
            man	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
   accidentally	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-MNR	(VP(ADVP*)
           shot	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
           face	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-LOC	*))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	*
      according	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-ADV	(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(PP*
        reports	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(NP(NP*)
           from	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-ADV	(NP*
          scene	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-ADV	*)))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

             He	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
            was	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
     reportedly	        RB	    B-ADJP	         O	              -	         O	(ADJP*
      conscious	        JJ	    E-ADJP	         O	              -	         O	*)
             as	        IN	    S-SBAR	         O	              -	         O	(SBAR*
      emergency	        NN	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A0	(S(NP*
          crews	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A0	*)
           took	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           took	       S-V	(VP*
            him	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A1	(NP*)
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	(PP*
           UPMC	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-PER	              -	      I-A2	(NP*
          Hamot	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-PER	              -	      E-A2	*))
            for	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-PNC	(PP*
      treatment	        NN	      S-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-PNC	(NP*))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

