     2017-04-06	        CD	      S-NP	         O	              -	(S1(NP*))

        17-year	       SYM	      S-NP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(S1(NP(ADJP*
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
            old	        JJ	         O	         O	              -	      S-A1	         O	*)
         killed	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	         killed	       S-V	         O	(UCP(S(VP*
          after	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	         O	(PP*
       shooting	       VBG	      S-VP	         O	       shooting	  I-AM-TMP	       S-V	(S(VP*
             on	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      B-A1	(PP*
          Crump	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	(NP*
           Road	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      E-A1	*)))))))
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	         O	*
            WMC	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      B-A1	(NP(NP*
         Action	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	*
           News	       NNP	      I-NP	     E-ORG	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	*
              5	        CD	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	*)
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	*
        Memphis	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	(NP(NP*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	  I-AM-TMP	      I-A1	*
      Tennessee	       NNP	      S-NP	     S-LOC	              -	  E-AM-TMP	      E-A1	(NP*))))))

              A	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A0	(S1(S(S(NP*
        17-year	        JJ	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	(ADJP*
              -	         :	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A0	*
            old	        JJ	         O	         O	              -	      E-A1	      E-A0	*))
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
           shot	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	           shot	       S-V	         O	(VP*
            and	        CC	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
         killed	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	         killed	         O	       S-V	*
       Thursday	       NNP	      B-NP	         O	              -	  B-AM-TMP	  B-AM-TMP	(NP*
      afternoon	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-TMP	  E-AM-TMP	*))))
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*
      according	       VBG	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(PP*
        Memphis	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-ORG	              -	         O	         O	(NP*
         Police	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-ORG	              -	         O	         O	*
     Department	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-ORG	              -	         O	         O	*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

  Investigators	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
           said	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           said	       S-V	         O	(VP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	      B-A1	(SBAR(S(NP*
       shooting	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A1	*)
         likely	        RB	      B-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	(ADVP*)
       happened	       VBD	      E-VP	         O	       happened	      I-A1	       S-V	(VP*
             in	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  B-AM-LOC	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
           area	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(PP*
          Crump	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP(NP*
           Road	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	*)
            and	        CC	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	*
           East	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	(NP*
         Raines	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A1	  I-AM-LOC	*
           Road	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A1	  E-AM-LOC	*)))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

             We	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      S-A0	         O	(S1(S(NP*)
          spoke	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	          spoke	       S-V	         O	(VP*
           with	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  B-AM-MNR	         O	(PP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	      B-A0	(NP(NP*
         friend	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	      E-A0	*)
             of	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	  I-AM-MNR	         O	(NP*
         victim	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	  E-AM-MNR	         O	*))))
           over	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(PP*
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A0	(NP(NP*
          phone	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      E-A0	*)
              ,	         ,	         O	         O	              -	      I-A1	         O	*
            who	        WP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	    S-R-A0	(SBAR(WHNP*)
           told	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	           told	      I-A1	       S-V	(S(VP*
             us	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      S-A2	(NP*)
            the	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      B-A1	(SBAR(S(NP*
         victim	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*)
            was	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(VP*
              a	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP(NP*
         junior	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*)
             at	        IN	      S-PP	         O	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(PP*
          Kirby	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	(NP*
           High	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A1	      I-A1	*
         School	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      E-A1	      E-A1	*))))))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	         O	(S1(S(NP*
         victim	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	         O	*)
            was	       VBD	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	         O	(VP*
         driven	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	         driven	       S-V	         O	(VP*
             to	        TO	      S-PP	         O	              -	      B-A2	         O	(PP*
            St.	       NNP	      B-NP	     B-LOC	              -	      I-A2	         O	(NP(NP*
        Francis	       NNP	      I-NP	     I-LOC	              -	      I-A2	         O	*
       Hospital	       NNP	      E-NP	     E-LOC	              -	      I-A2	         O	*)
          where	       WRB	    S-ADVP	         O	              -	      I-A2	         O	(SBAR(WHADVP*)
        doctors	       NNS	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	      S-A0	(S(NP*)
     pronounced	       VBD	      S-VP	         O	     pronounced	      I-A2	       S-V	(VP*
            him	       PRP	      S-NP	         O	              -	      I-A2	      S-A1	(S(NP*)
           dead	        JJ	    S-ADJP	         O	              -	      E-A2	      S-A2	(ADJP*)))))))))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	         O	*))

            The	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         victim	        NN	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
           ’s	        JJ	      I-NP	         O	              -	      I-A1	*
       identity	        NN	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
            has	       VBZ	      B-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
            not	        RB	      I-VP	         O	              -	  S-AM-NEG	*
           been	       VBN	      I-VP	         O	              -	         O	(VP*
       released	       VBN	      E-VP	         O	       released	       S-V	(VP*)))
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

            All	        DT	      B-NP	         O	              -	      B-A1	(S1(S(NP*
         rights	       NNS	      E-NP	         O	              -	      E-A1	*)
       reserved	       VBN	      S-VP	         O	       reserved	       S-V	(VP*)
              .	         .	         O	         O	              -	         O	*))

